(Sheldon:)Yes, and do you know what
the odds are I'd pick your name?
(Raj:)-No.
one in five.
(Sheldon:)Now you know why I'm pouting.
(Raj(over walkie-talkie):)All right, teams.
Get ready to open your first puzzle.
(Bernadette:)Go!
(Raj(over walkie-talkie):)Do you see what I did?
The Hrs! puzzle is a puzzle!
(Raj(over walkie-talkie):)Oh, my God, how adorable is that?
(Raj(over walkie-talkie):)I wish I had a friend like me.
(Sheldon:)What are you doing?
You have to start with the edges.
(Penny:)There's no right way, Sheldon.
I already found a few pieces that tit.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, take them apart
and start with the edges.
(Sheldon:)And stop wasting time.
(Howard:)Wow, you're really good at puzzles.
(Amy:)I did them all the time as a kid.
(Amy:)As my mom used to say,
"When you're doing a puzzle,
it's like having a thousand friends."
(Amy:)She was full
of fun lies like that.
(Howard:)If it makes you feel any better,
my mom's just full of pound cake.